A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Audiovisual Materials, 1966-1976; 1
  - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Radio and Television - "Beautify America" - Cuts 1-12, 1966 June; 1/4 audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 15605)
    Produced with the cooperation of the White House by the radio stations of the Storer Broadcasting Company. Introductions by Jim Ameche.
  - Rockefeller Family & Associates/Rockefeller Family Office - Public Affairs - Ira Liebowitz Interview, Air dates: 1974 December 2 and 8; 29 minutes; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 15606)
    General
    Contained a types letter to Nelson Rockefeller from Denise Krumm, Program Cccordinator/ Ultravision Broadcasting Company, Inc., dated November 22,
    "Dear Sir, Enclosed is an audio tape recording of a public service program which was recorded today for our playback on December 2nd and December 8th, 1974
    The guest on the show, Ira Liebowitz, made strong accusations about you and we felt that you would want to listen to this tape.
    If you wish to respond we will make our station available to you at your convenience."
    (Handwritten on top: "No reply")
- Archives, Tioga Photographs, 1037
  Photographs
  - Richford - JDR Birthplace (Box 14, Folder 180)
    Scope and Contents note
    Richford, JDR, houses, landscape
  - William Avery Rockefeller -William Levingston Report - Joseph W. Ernst (Box 14, Folder 181)
    Levingston home, Cemeteries, Graves, Ranches, Illinois, North Dakota